<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Wine | Episodes of Sleep]]></title>
  <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/categories/wine/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-04-03T00:23:30-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Anthony Kang]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Break]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/14/spring-break/"/>
    <updated>2015-03-14T21:43:53-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/14/spring-break</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
    Spring break finally started, so either I&#8217;ll use this extra time to make higher quality posts for all of my 3 readers, or I&#8217;ll just embrace my laziness.
</p>


<p>
    This morning I actually had a pretty interesting dream but I was too lazy to write it down. All I remember was this time I wasn&#8217;t participating in my dream, I was simply watching it unfold upon me from inside my head.
</p>


<h2>Pi day</h2>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/pies_3_14.png" width="400" height="400"></p>

<p>
    Happy Pi day. Don&#8217;t deny my R^2 Pi huehue. Anyways, friend swiped me in to dining court this morning and since Purdue is fat(phat) as fuck, look at these fucking pies. Ok top left, standard pumpkin pie. Not that interesting, but good nontheless. Bottom left, we got some coconut cream pie. Very light, but also very sweet. Strong coconut flavor. Top right, is it really a pie if its just chocolate pudding? Well it&#8217;s like chocolate pudding on the standard graham cracker crust, and its topped with some peanut butter m & m&#8217;s mmm.  Now the bottom right, this one was a fucking delicacy. So everyone&#8217;s familiar with mint chocolate chip ice cream, so this green colored filling is kind of like mint flavored pudding and its fucking good. Underneath that its not crust, its chocolate fudge. Yea you heard it here first.
</p>


<p>mmmm Liver</p>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/liver_3_13.png" width="400" height="400">
<img class="center" src="/images/dinner_3_13.png" width="400" height="400"></p>

<p>
    Liver looks gross. But liver is fucking good. But it also tastes like fucking liver. But you know what I really enjoyed, look at the little bit of red shit at the top of the picture. That&#8217;s the blood I harvested from the liver and turned in to a sauce. No I&#8217;m kidding that&#8217;s just some chili garlic sauce that I have that reminded me of home. NOT SIRACHA, that chili sauce that comes in a little container on the tables of chinese restaurants.
</p>


<h3>I swear I&#8217;m not a girl</h3>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/wine_3_13.png" width="200" height="200"></p>

<p>
    Drank this with my roomate. It basically tastes like sprite. Good stuff overall though I have to say.
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
