<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: School | Episodes of Sleep]]></title>
  <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/categories/school/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-03-31T23:12:56-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Anthony Kang]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Out There Grindin]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/04/out-there-grindin/"/>
    <updated>2015-03-04T23:57:54-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/04/out-there-grindin</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Almost failed a class today so I don&rsquo;t even feel like posting but shout out to Archit for saving my life.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Got Smashed on an Interview]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/02/got-smashed-on-an-interview/"/>
    <updated>2015-03-02T23:32:12-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/02/got-smashed-on-an-interview</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div>
<h3>Grand theft of my breath</h3>
    <p>
        All right you guys are in for a fucking story today, I actually remembered my dream and wrote stuff to help me remember. First of all, in a lot of my dreams I&#8217;m typically put in to the kind of scenario similar to GTA. If you&#8217;ve played GTA before, if you don&#8217;t have cheats enabled, when you actually get wanted stars, the police chase after you and you actually have to hide. But that&#8217;s just a video game, imagine you&#8217;re in that scenario in your dream. When I dream, they&#8217;re lucid in the sense that I&#8217;m conscious of whats going on, and the fact that I&#8217;m dreaming, but not in the sense where I can control my dream. I can control my actions, but within the real life limits of the scene I&#8217;m dumped in to. So I&#8217;m part of some 4 man hunter team and we&#8217;re wanted by the police and we&#8217;re at my old high school. We&#8217;re sneaking around and I just feel it in my heart that we&#8217;re fucked so I just book it and run through the school, through class rooms and doors and gyms and climbing shit and I eventually make it and hide in a tree. The thing is I actually feel the nervousness and heart papulations you would get if this was actually happening. For some reason I&#8217;m always fucking running away from something in my dreams.
    </p>
    <p>
        The second part of my dream was even more fucked up. I&#8217;m still part of this four man team, but we&#8217;re thrown in some labyrinth to hunt another 4 man team. Or rather, we&#8217;re also being hunted. So we had some gear where we could share vision with each other, so I saw when one of my team mates was pinned against a wall staring down the barrel of an enemy charging her laser beams. But because this is a dream, my teammate did something absolutely crazy and somehow opened a dimension portal where she was and where another enemy was and swapped positions. So then the enemy was going to shoot her own teammates. But my teammate fucked up and the portal she opened closed on her arm, but she didin&#8217;t lose her arm, she just lost the soul within her arm&#8230; So she tried to recover it by siphoning some soul from another teammate. But that teammate was being hunted and he was hiding from his hunter by making clones of himself so his hunter could not figure out which was the real one, but when my first teammate tried linking her soul with him, it gave away which of the clones was real. I was thinking to myself shit she fucked everything up, and then I woke up. Dreams pretty fucking real&#8230;.
    </p>
</div>


<div>
    <h2>I can make a better looking one (promise)</h2>
    <img class="center" src="/images/breakfast_3_2.png" width="350" height="350">
    <p>I was dam tired this morning, so presentation and precision was at an absolute minimum when making this egg sandwich.</p>
</div>


<div>
    <p>
        Remeber when I said my group wanted to make a GPU on an FPGA. Well we decided since we know nothing about FPGAs and nothing about GPUs we&#8217;re just going to do triple DES encryption on an FPGA instead. That way we&#8217;re only completely clueless on half the project.
    </p>
    <p>
        I also started replaying Fire Emblem: Sacred Stones today, that games bomb.
    </p>
</div>


<div>
    <h2>Roasted Chicken Drumsticks</h2>
    <img class="center" src="/images/lunch_3_2.png" width="400" height="400">
    <p>
        Working on the chest today so I made some chicken for lunch. 
        I think the best way to impart flavor on meat isn&#8217;t with a marinade, or seasoning, or sauce, but my perfectly cooking the meat to exact tenderness. Exact doneness. Not overcooked or undercooked, but precisely cooked. And that is what you see here. FUCK YEAAAAA (Ok it&#8217;s a tad undercooked but I was hungry)
    </p>
    <p>
        I&#8217;ll post some recipes enventually.
    </p>
</div>


<div>
    <h2>Informatica Interview</h2>
    <p>
        So I had a second round interview with Informatica today for the software developer position, and I felt decently confident going in to it because I had already been offered by Amazon (pure luck). I&#8217;m pretty confident with all data structure oreinted questions, but today I was thrown a pretty big curve ball and I just ended up being stomped on. I don&#8217;t know if I just wasn&#8217;t feeling it today, but either way this was pretty humbling.
    </p>
    <p>
        Given an n-ary tree where root nodes can have multiple children, nodes can share children, and children can share parents, reverse the tree and return a list of the leaf nodes. 
    </p>
    <p>
        I couldn&#8217;t solve it within the time limit, and even after working out the problem after the interview, I still don&#8217;t fully understand it. 
    </p>
    <p>
        Here&#8217;s a good <a href="http://www.careercup.com/question?id=12219054">thread</a> on the question. 
    </p>
</div>


<div>
    <h2>Chinese Smoked Beef</h2>
    <img class="center" src="/images/dinner_3_2.png" width="400" height="400">
    <p>
        So my dad sent me some chinese style smoked beef brisket. So unlike the American BBQ style brisket, the chinese or perhaps taiwanese style is alot firmer. Also it&#8217;s usually eaten chilled or at room temperature. But the point is it&#8217;s fucking good and its fucking dense and I might have eaten like a full pound of it for dinner. It&#8217;s hiding under the brocolli which I added to help push the beef out the other end. 
    </p>
</div>


<p>
    I was kinda sad beacuse the Warriors lost today, freaking Jarret Jack. But shout out to Captain Kirk for making me feel better. 
    <video  preload='metadata' controls ><source src='/videos/bbal_3_2.mp4' type='video/mp4; codecs="avc1.42E01E, mp4a.40.2"'></video>
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protect the Freaking Ball]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/02/26/protect-the-freaking-ball/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-26T23:30:12-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/02/26/protect-the-freaking-ball</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><body></p>

<div>
    I freaking had three episodes of dreams last night but I messed up and didin&#8217;t write them down before making breakfast so I only remember one. I&#8217;m going to start setting up the tomorrow&#8217;s posts so I can just slap them down on the post in the morning.
    <br/>
    <br/>
    <h3>I&#8217;m transferring???</h3>
    <div>
        So the only dream I remember involved me getting an email in my Purdue email saying that I&#8217;m being transferred to a private local college back home, and I had no choice but to go. When I arrived in my hometown, all my buds from home had been extracted from their respecitve colleges and we were forced to take a placement test. So this isn&#8217;t very exciting, but the thing is that I remember the test with such detail. I was doing freaking combinatorics problems, drawing RTL diagrams, writing code, and doing IQ test questions. When I woke up I actually said wtf because at one point I was deriving a formula for a summation on paper, like that&#8217;s shit I can&#8217;t even do when I&#8217;m awake&#8230; I&#8217;m sure my other dreams were more #action_packed but I had to make breakfast. 
    </div>
    <h2>It has bread this time</h2>
    <div><img class="center" src="/images/breakfast_2_26.png" width="350" height="350"></div>
    <div>
        Last cajun suasage. I promise you guys I&#8217;ll get a different kind of sausage tomorrow. I had some peanut butter sandwiches today too since I had to skip lunch. I&#8217;ll admit I licked the melted peanut butter off my wrists like a savage.
    </div>
    <h2>My chuttigabro Utpal</h2>
    <div><img class="center" src="/images/state_diagram_2_26.png" width="350" height="350"></div>
    <div>
        So I had a totally messed up state diagram drawing so when I was creating the controller module I already knew I was fucked. So shoutout to my TA Utpal for drawing this masterpiece of a state transition diagram for me.
    </div>
    <h2>Ball is life?</h2>
    <div>
        So the team I played with the first couple games today could hardly inbound the ball&#8230; We made these guys look like the Golden State Warriors.
    </div>
    <div><video  preload='metadata' controls ><source src='/videos/sloppy_gif_2_26_converted.mp4' type='video/mp4; codecs="avc1.42E01E, mp4a.40.2"'></video></div>
    <div>
        Later my asian niggas came and we styled on the opposition so that was good. People at Purdue take too many stop up threes. No one ever wants to run the good ol pick and roll or cut to the rim. But everyone plays with really good effort so the games are still awesome. We&#8217;re lucky we have ten courts at our rec center. 
    </div>
    <h2>Spaghetti Carbonara (not really)</h2>
    <div><img class="center" src="/images/dinner_2_26.png" width="350" height="350"></div>
    <div>
        The only Carbonara thing about this pasta was that I used bacon. But I also used the leftover roast pork I had so the porkfat melted in with the bacon fat and then what more can I say. I added some spinach and red onion to make it healthy.
    </div>
</div>


<p></body></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sat Down on the Test Bench]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/02/25/sat-down-on-the-test-bench/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-25T22:48:46-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/02/25/sat-down-on-the-test-bench</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><body>
    <div>
        So I&rsquo;ve been playing this game on my phone called Crossy Street where you&rsquo;re basically a cute little animal and you try to cross streets frogger style. So I dreamt I was a dam duck trying to cross a street full of cars trying to kill me. And some dude in my dream kept trying to tell me that closing tags were unnecessary. Nightmares of making pages with Jade I guess.
    </div>
    <h2> Cajun Sausage Eggs (Again) </h2>
    <div><img class="center" src="/images/breakfast_2_25.png" width="350" height="350"></div>
    <div>
        I told you guys I eat this shit every dam day. I&rsquo;m excited to wake up in the morning and eat this. I promise I&rsquo;ll have new type of sausage soon I&rsquo;m running out of the cajun ones. But today I found a freaking size large egg in my box of jumbo eggs. Dam Purdue market tryna rip me.
    </div>
    <br/>
    <div>
        Today&rsquo;s software tools lab challenge for my ECE364 class was to write a bunch of functions to parse an XML document with regex. If you&rsquo;ve used regex before, then it&rsquo;s obvious how powerful it can be, but also how convuluted the patterns can be. I mean, look at this ip address match:
        <div>
            <figure class='code'><div class="highlight"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre class="line-numbers"><span class='line-number'>1</span>
</pre></td><td class='code'><pre><code class='python'><span class='line'><span class="n">m</span> <span class="o">=</span> <span class="n">re</span><span class="o">.</span><span class="n">match</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="s">r&#39;(25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)(.(25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}:([0-9]{1,4}|[12][0-9]{4}|3[01][0-9]{3}|32[0-6][0-9]{2}|327[0-5][0-9]|3276[0-7])&amp;lsquo;,line)</span>
</span></code></pre></td></tr></table></div></figure>
        </div>
        Maybe I&rsquo;m weird but I think coming up with Regex patterns is kind of fun heheh. After lab me and my chut Jakshay went to get some gyros.
        <h2>Captain Gyro</h2>
        <div><img class="center" src="/images/lunch_2_25.png" width="350" height="350"></div>
        <div>
            Its harder to find diversified cuisine here in Indiana but Captain Gyro is an exception. It&rsquo;s owned by some old dude straight out of Greece and he&rsquo;s got one of those rotating spools of gyro meat and he shaves that shit straight in to some pita bread and its on point. The sandwich here is has extra vegetables (gotta get that fiber) but its filled with meat. No nonsense homemade gyro&rsquo;s.
        </div>
        <h2>Sit Down Boi</h2>
        <div><img class="center" src="/images/lab_2_25.png" width="450" height="450"></div>
        <div>
            I wish I knew what I was getting myself in to when I said I wanted to be a computer engineer. I was not ready to deal with all this hardware stuff. Who the hell wants to write a test bench for this monstrosity. Looking at the mapped design makes me need to sit down. I&rsquo;ll probably appreciate timing problems and meta stable states as I progress&hellip;or maybe not.
        </div>
        <h2>Bacon Fried Rice</h2>
        <div><img class="center" src="/images/dinner_2_25.png" width="450" height="450"></div>
        <div>
            You can&rsquo;t see the bacon but that shit was on sale and it&rsquo;s in there and yes its good. All you see are veggies cause I&rsquo;m all about those veggies. I&rsquo;ll break out the wok one day to make some legit fried rice but today I was just hungry so this is all there is. Ok, I&rsquo;m eating some thin mints as I write this.<br/>
        </div>
    </div></p>

<p></body></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circuits Suck]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/02/24/circuits-suck/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-24T18:29:20-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/02/24/circuits-suck</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><body></p>

<div>
Didn&#8217;t remember my dream from last night. Circuits suck. Stared at a breadboard for two hours only to realize the circuit wasn&#8217;t working because my transistor had blown. The hardware struggles of a software oriented computer engineer continues. But enough of that, on to the food (I need to work on plating).
</div>


<h2> Cajun Sausage Disco Eggs </h2>


<div><img class="center" src="/images/breakfast_2_24.png" width="500" height="500"></div>


<div> Pretty much make this every morning. It&#8217;s fucking good and it lasts me until lunch. Gotta have that breakfast. </div>


<p><br/></p>

<div>I had a homemade roast pork sandwich for lunch but that wasn&#8217;t worth taking a picture of. Currently using my phones camera which is quite&#8230;.. shitty.</div>


<p><br/></p>

<h2> Soy Sauce Roast Pork </h2>


<div><img class="center" src="/images/dinner_2_24.png" width="500" height="500"></div>


<div> Meat, rice, and brocolli. The plating sucks but it tastes good I swear. It&#8217;s easy to make too, I&#8217;ll try to get a recipe up eventually.</div>


<p><br/></p>

<h2> Daily Workout </h2>


<div>Wanted to get a video of a 4 plate pull but definitly wasn&#8217;t feeling it today. Form was already struggling with 315 x 5. Going to take a break from lifting for a week and probably just play ball. I think I need a better chair for my desk cause my back&#8217;s been feeling like an old man&#8217;s. </div>


<p><video  preload='metadata' controls ><source src='/videos/dl_2_25_2015.mp4' type='video/mp4; codecs="avc1.42E01E, mp4a.40.2"'></video></p>

<div>Here&#8217;s a some pictures I wanted to put on this blog but I didin&#8217;t have it set up yet and I&#8217;m too lazy now ></div>


<p><br/></p>

<div>
stole some chicken from the dining court
<img class="center" src="/images/dc_chicken_2_22.png" width="500" height="500">
lamb spaghetti with some unmelted cheese
<img class="center" src="/images/dinner_2_23.png" width="500" height="500">
4 dollar vegeterian wet burritos with my chut jakshay
<img class="center" src="/images/jakshay_2_23.png" width="500" height="500">
<img class="center" src="/images/lunch_2_23.png" width="500" height="500">
</div>


<p></body></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
