<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Dream | Episodes of Sleep]]></title>
  <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/categories/dream/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-03-02T01:01:33-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Anthony Kang]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[House of Cards S3!!]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/02/28/house-of-cards-s3/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-28T23:00:05-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/02/28/house-of-cards-s3</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Anyone tryna binge watch some HOC</p>


<h3>I support GMOs in my dream</h3>


<div>
    So last night I came up with an awesome invention, pasta that changes color based on the heat of the sauce. By heat I mean spiciness. So if you have some tomato sauce, the actual spaghetti, or in my dream it was like the spiral pasta you get from sweet tomatoes or soupplantation, gets more red depending on the spiciness of the sauce. So maybe like the flour has some molecule that can detect capsaicin or something and that releases a red pigment. Ok it&#8217;s pretty stupid but I can see this being pretty popular. 
    </div>


<h2>Got some new sausage</h2>


<p>
    <img class="left" src="/images/sausages_2_28.png" width="370" height="400">
    <img class="right" src="/images/lunch_2_28.png" width="370" height="400">
</p>


<p></p>

<h2>&nbsp</h2>


<div>
    As promised, I got some new sausages. Tailgater&#8217;s brats straight from the boilermaker butcher block. I don&#8217;t rememebr the flavor profile but I do know it was dam good. Added some ketchuip and siracha on my eggs, and you know I like that penaut butter slightly melted. 
</div>


<p></br></p>

<p>If anyone knows about OrCad and using Pspice with that, fuck that shit.</p>


<h2>Smoked Chicken Leg</h2>


<p>
    <img class="center" src="/images/dinner_2_28.png" width="350" height="350">
</p>


<p>
    So my dad sent me some bomb ass smoked chicken leg. He literally wrapped that shit in plastic wrap and sent it half way across the country hoping it would not spoil, and thank god it didin&#8217;t cause it was dynamite. And I made some bacon and chicken spaghetti with some tomato sauce, but the pasta wasn&#8217;t from my dream unfortunately. Brocolli for &#8220;health&#8221;
</p>


<p></br></p>

<p>
    Oh if anyone is really familiar with the Chinese Remainder Theorem hit me up cause I need some help with that.
</p>


<p></br></p>

<p>
    I&#8217;ve been balling every day this week since I&#8217;m taking a break from lifting. So I have a little blurb every day. Today I matched up with this huge black dude cause I was the tallest on my team. But this guy was like 6&#8217;3&#8221; and I&#8217;m 5&#8217;10&#8221; on a good day and when he was backing me down his ass was straight in my chest. But after the game he told me I gave him a lot of trouble on defense so even though I felt I was being backed down by Shaq I guess I still played some good D. 
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fuck Hearthstone Man]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/02/27/fuck-heathstone-man/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-27T00:59:56-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/02/27/fuck-heathstone-man</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><body>
    <h3>Secret Saudi Dance Party</h3>
    <div>
        Ok so the dream started of with me walking towards my apartment from the electrical engineering lab and somehow I saw my buddy Allen from back home. Like this guy is straight out of my home town and I&rsquo;d consider him one of my closest friends. He says he&rsquo;s here on a secret spy mission and I end up taking him to the Stewert Center where there&rsquo;s a secret dance bar and inside the bar there&rsquo;s a secret room where he has to dance to prevent the launching of missles. On the way there we pass the Saudi Arabian Embassy somehow. We enter the dance bar and it&rsquo;s quite empty. There were only a couple of circles formed but no one was really going at it. All of a sudden Allen transforms in to a female version of himself and then he starts going nuts randomly on the floor by himself. Somehow we make it to the secret room where I was put in charge of running test benches for underclassmen code and for some reason my life was on the line if they worked or not. So I decided to also dance but I felt super weak and could not pull of any of my typical moves and then Allen transformed in to some fusion of my girlfriend Theresa and Byron where that   person would not cuddle with me and was constantly playing some stupid iteration of the online game Tera.
        <br/>
        I&rsquo;m just rambling but that&rsquo;s what it is bois.
    </div>
    <h2>Ran out of sausage</h2>
    <div><img class="center" src="/images/breakfast_2_27.png" width="350" height="350"></div>
    <div>
        Mixing it up with some store bought on sale bacon and some sunny side up eggs. Messed one up cause I cracked it from too high.
    </div>
    <h2>RSA Cryptography</h2>
    <div><img class="center" src="/images/rsa_2_27.png" width="350" height="350"></div>
    <div>
        I worked on writing a script that performs RSA cryptography encryption and decryption for the better part of my day, so if you&rsquo;re wondering how the keys are generated this is it. Totient is a funny word hehe.
    </div>
    <h2>I ain&rsquo;t Indian Lentils</h2>
    <div><img class="center" src="/images/lunch_2_27.png" width="350" height="350"></div>
    <div>
        Tried making some lentils today, but I used too much water and the consistency was messed up. It&rsquo;s got garam masala, cumin, coriander, and chili powder. And of course spinach for &ldquo;health&rdquo;.
    </div>
    <div>I&rsquo;m outta control</div>
    <div>
        Played ball with my buds today. So much more fun when you&rsquo;re playing with everyone you know, the team dynamic awesome. Not gonna lie I was going hard and going off today, a little like Brodie.
    </div>
    <div><video  preload='metadata' controls ><source src='/videos/bbal_2_28.mp4' type='video/mp4; codecs="avc1.42E01E, mp4a.40.2"'></video></div>
    <div>
        Except I&rsquo;m not Brodie so the result is now my knee hurts like a mofo.
    </div>
    <h2>Coupons for days</h2>
    <div>
        Now usually you all know I&rsquo;m about that healthy life (spinach), but when you got buy one get one coupons for McDonalds, you know what it is.
    </div>
    <div><img class="center" src="/images/dinner_2_27.png" width="350" height="350"></div>
    <div>
        Nutritional content claims I had almost 2000mg of sodium, which must explain why I&rsquo;m so thirsty right now.
    </div>
    <h2>Boring Hearthstone Meta</h2>
    <div>
        Hearthstone is such a drag right now. Everyclass runs a max of 2 viable lists for the ladder and the game is so predictable. If both you and your opponent know how to play your decks correctly, it simply becomes a matchup and hand draw coinflip. I&rsquo;m not an expert, that&rsquo;s just my opinion from watching the recent tournaments as well as from my experiences on the ladder. And off course there&rsquo;s Dr. Bitch.
    </div>
    <div><img class="center" src="/images/dr_bitch_2_28.png"></div>
</body></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protect the Freaking Ball]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/02/26/protect-the-freaking-ball/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-26T23:30:12-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/02/26/protect-the-freaking-ball</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><body></p>

<div>
    I freaking had three episodes of dreams last night but I messed up and didin&#8217;t write them down before making breakfast so I only remember one. I&#8217;m going to start setting up the tomorrow&#8217;s posts so I can just slap them down on the post in the morning.
    <br/>
    <br/>
    <h3>I&#8217;m transferring???</h3>
    <div>
        So the only dream I remember involved me getting an email in my Purdue email saying that I&#8217;m being transferred to a private local college back home, and I had no choice but to go. When I arrived in my hometown, all my buds from home had been extracted from their respecitve colleges and we were forced to take a placement test. So this isn&#8217;t very exciting, but the thing is that I remember the test with such detail. I was doing freaking combinatorics problems, drawing RTL diagrams, writing code, and doing IQ test questions. When I woke up I actually said wtf because at one point I was deriving a formula for a summation on paper, like that&#8217;s shit I can&#8217;t even do when I&#8217;m awake&#8230; I&#8217;m sure my other dreams were more #action_packed but I had to make breakfast. 
    </div>
    <h2>It has bread this time</h2>
    <div><img class="center" src="/images/breakfast_2_26.png" width="350" height="350"></div>
    <div>
        Last cajun suasage. I promise you guys I&#8217;ll get a different kind of sausage tomorrow. I had some peanut butter sandwiches today too since I had to skip lunch. I&#8217;ll admit I licked the melted peanut butter off my wrists like a savage.
    </div>
    <h2>My chuttigabro Utpal</h2>
    <div><img class="center" src="/images/state_diagram_2_26.png" width="350" height="350"></div>
    <div>
        So I had a totally messed up state diagram drawing so when I was creating the controller module I already knew I was fucked. So shoutout to my TA Utpal for drawing this masterpiece of a state transition diagram for me.
    </div>
    <h2>Ball is life?</h2>
    <div>
        So the team I played with the first couple games today could hardly inbound the ball&#8230; We made these guys look like the Golden State Warriors.
    </div>
    <div><video  preload='metadata' controls ><source src='/videos/sloppy_gif_2_26_converted.mp4' type='video/mp4; codecs="avc1.42E01E, mp4a.40.2"'></video></div>
    <div>
        Later my asian niggas came and we styled on the opposition so that was good. People at Purdue take too many stop up threes. No one ever wants to run the good ol pick and roll or cut to the rim. But everyone plays with really good effort so the games are still awesome. We&#8217;re lucky we have ten courts at our rec center. 
    </div>
    <h2>Spaghetti Carbonara (not really)</h2>
    <div><img class="center" src="/images/dinner_2_26.png" width="350" height="350"></div>
    <div>
        The only Carbonara thing about this pasta was that I used bacon. But I also used the leftover roast pork I had so the porkfat melted in with the bacon fat and then what more can I say. I added some spinach and red onion to make it healthy.
    </div>
</div>


<p></body></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
