<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Dream | Episodes of Sleep]]></title>
  <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/categories/dream/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-03-10T00:40:50-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Anthony Kang]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacker or Programmer]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/07/hacker-or-programmer/"/>
    <updated>2015-03-07T17:09:47-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/07/hacker-or-programmer</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Double post today since I missed a post yesterday because I was at a hackathon.</p>

<h3>Zombie Apocalypse</h3>


<p>
    I actually had to do a google search on apocalypse to make sure I spelled it correctly and magically I did. But this dream was freaking brazy, yea, crazy not brazy. So brazy I remembered it even it was two nights ago. So I me and my buddy Erik were somewhere in China visiting our buddy Jason. And everything seemed really normal, just chilling and going around China but for some reason we spent a lot of time on the subways. Like the the only places that felt safe in the country were on the subways, but even then, there was some kind of uncomfortable aura from being on the subway. Somehow, the entire universe we were in became some sort of zombie apocalypse world. In my dreams I&#8217;m always thrown in to these being chased situations where I have to run away. So Erik and I were actually with a bunch of other people and we were running away but they couldn&#8217;t keep up with me cause we had to parkor over trucks for some reason, so I guess I just kept running and I left them behind. I didin&#8217;t ditch them, I just needed to figure out a way out of this. I saw a family of four enter a bathroom and then I saw a light flash from underneath the door. I opened the bathroom door and they were gone, all that was left was a menu on the toilet seat. On the menu was an option for &#8220;go home.&#8221; So I guess I just ordered that and I was teleported back home. But then I knew I had to go back and get Erik and the others so I used the menu to order myself back in to the zombie world&#8230;. I ran out of the bathroom holding the menu and I saw the others and they said &#8220;Anthony! we found a way to get back home! We have to hold each other&#8217;s hand and run to Wal-Mart where there&#8217;s a portal!&#8221; Well I said fuck that cause I have this menu.
</p>


<h2>Tortilla Espanola (kind of)</h2>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/breakfast_3_6.png" width="400" height="400"></p>

<p>Basically an egg omlette with bacon, spinach, SAUSAGE, and rice.</p>


<h2>Hack the Anvil</h2>


<p>
    Went to an hackathon with my buds, but I guess I don&#8217;t have the same fire as the other hackers there so we left early. I mean I really enjoy programming and creating new things, and trying out new technologies, but I guess I do enjoy it enough to go for 36 hours straight. I mean, I want to play basketball and eat real food, not the chain store pizza they provide for us. But it was still a good expereince, I got to try out a Myo, which is an arm band that reacts to different ways you flex your arm, to send specific inputs to a program.
</p>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/myo_3_6.png" width="400" height="400"></p>

<h2>the next day</h2>


<p>
    Ok so my dream from last night, which was after the hackathon, involved me doing pushups and somehow kicking my mom in the face. So we&#8217;ll just leave it at that.
</p>


<h2>Boiler Block Bacon</h2>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/breakfast_3_7.png" width="350" height="350"></p>

<p>
    Made an actual omlette today instead of my weird half scramble half omlette thing. And some nice, meaty bacon from the Purdue butcher shop. And I also like peanut butter.
</p>


<p>
    I have 5 consecutive midterms the following week so I mainly just studied today. Gotta know those pdfs, cdfs, and pmfs. But at the same time that didin&#8217;t stop me from playing 4 hours of basketball today. UGHHHHHHH
</p>


<h2>Spaghetti cooked in meat juice</h2>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/dinner_3_7.png" width="400" height="400"></p>

<p>
    So I had some leftover meat juice from cooking that huge ass steak the other day, as well as the steak, so I decided to cook the spaghetti in that meat juice. This was hands down the best fucking spaghetti I&#8217;ve ever made for myself. I think everything should just be cooked in meat juice. 
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Slice of Cow]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/05/slice-of-cow/"/>
    <updated>2015-03-05T23:03:33-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/05/slice-of-cow</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
    I deemed my dream good enough to take notes on it in the morning, so let&#8217;s see if I can recall it based on my notes. Ok so there&#8217;s this one plaza in cupertino or sunnyvale or I don&#8217;t even know where somewhere around that area, and that plaza has like a Japanese store, and a beard papa. So I was driving there to meet my family, but my car was driving freaking weird, it had no handling. So if you&#8217;ve played mario kart before, it&#8217;s like my car had like a handling rating of 1 out of 10. I couldn&#8217;t make turns for shit. But like I said before I don&#8217;t simply dream, I freaking expereince the feelings, so imagine driving a car that you can&#8217;t turn, and you can&#8217;t slow down, on a regular road. But whatever I finally make it to the dam blaza and there&#8217;s a gym like barbell brigade, bart kwan&#8217;s gym, except everyone working out in the gym was naked. So there were people walking around in the parking lot naked so I don&#8217;t know, instead of going what the fuck I actually was just like ok I&#8217;m down and went to work out in there. All I really remember was the dream was fucking crazy, and this one person had boobs as muscles, if you can imagine that. Also next door was a store selling like pounds of smoked turkey wrapped in plastic wrap. I just kept thinking of fermented meat when I woke up.
</p>


<h2>Breakfast Tacos</h2>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/breakfast_3_5.png" width="400" height="400"></p>

<p>
    Only had one egg today so I couldn&#8217;t make the usual. I needed to eat some carbs also because I had to skip lunch, so insert the tacos.
</p>


<h2>steak on steak on steak</h2>


<p>
    So I had a cut of beef that was about 1.5ft long and 1ft wide so the only way to cook it was in the oven. I pretty much steamed it for around 10 minutes and then braised it dry for another ten minutes and it came out perfect. My camera sucks (or I suck at taking pictures).
</p>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/beef_3_5.png" width="400" height="400"></p>

<p>
    It&#8217;s sitting in its own meat juice, and the inside of that marrow is all melted (can&#8217;t wait to eat that). Cut up with some brocolli for health.
</p>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/dinner_3_5.png" width="400" height="400"></p>

<p>
    My dad sent me this cute little thing.
</p>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/hotsauce_3_5.png" width="350" height="350"></p>

<p>
    As you can see its only 22mL. I thought it would be crazy spicy, but it&#8217;s actually really good. It&#8217;s actually really dam good. Its not like those other habanero sauces that just focus on being spicy, or other hot sauces that are overly vinergry. This sauce just straight up tastes like chilis, it has flavor, and it&#8217;s spicy without being overwhelming.
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Got Smashed on an Interview]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/02/got-smashed-on-an-interview/"/>
    <updated>2015-03-02T23:32:12-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/02/got-smashed-on-an-interview</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div>
<h3>Grand theft of my breath</h3>
    <p>
        All right you guys are in for a fucking story today, I actually remembered my dream and wrote stuff to help me remember. First of all, in a lot of my dreams I&#8217;m typically put in to the kind of scenario similar to GTA. If you&#8217;ve played GTA before, if you don&#8217;t have cheats enabled, when you actually get wanted stars, the police chase after you and you actually have to hide. But that&#8217;s just a video game, imagine you&#8217;re in that scenario in your dream. When I dream, they&#8217;re lucid in the sense that I&#8217;m conscious of whats going on, and the fact that I&#8217;m dreaming, but not in the sense where I can control my dream. I can control my actions, but within the real life limits of the scene I&#8217;m dumped in to. So I&#8217;m part of some 4 man hunter team and we&#8217;re wanted by the police and we&#8217;re at my old high school. We&#8217;re sneaking around and I just feel it in my heart that we&#8217;re fucked so I just book it and run through the school, through class rooms and doors and gyms and climbing shit and I eventually make it and hide in a tree. The thing is I actually feel the nervousness and heart papulations you would get if this was actually happening. For some reason I&#8217;m always fucking running away from something in my dreams.
    </p>
    <p>
        The second part of my dream was even more fucked up. I&#8217;m still part of this four man team, but we&#8217;re thrown in some labyrinth to hunt another 4 man team. Or rather, we&#8217;re also being hunted. So we had some gear where we could share vision with each other, so I saw when one of my team mates was pinned against a wall staring down the barrel of an enemy charging her laser beams. But because this is a dream, my teammate did something absolutely crazy and somehow opened a dimension portal where she was and where another enemy was and swapped positions. So then the enemy was going to shoot her own teammates. But my teammate fucked up and the portal she opened closed on her arm, but she didin&#8217;t lose her arm, she just lost the soul within her arm&#8230; So she tried to recover it by siphoning some soul from another teammate. But that teammate was being hunted and he was hiding from his hunter by making clones of himself so his hunter could not figure out which was the real one, but when my first teammate tried linking her soul with him, it gave away which of the clones was real. I was thinking to myself shit she fucked everything up, and then I woke up. Dreams pretty fucking real&#8230;.
    </p>
</div>


<div>
    <h2>I can make a better looking one (promise)</h2>
    <img class="center" src="/images/breakfast_3_2.png" width="350" height="350">
    <p>I was dam tired this morning, so presentation and precision was at an absolute minimum when making this egg sandwich.</p>
</div>


<div>
    <p>
        Remeber when I said my group wanted to make a GPU on an FPGA. Well we decided since we know nothing about FPGAs and nothing about GPUs we&#8217;re just going to do triple DES encryption on an FPGA instead. That way we&#8217;re only completely clueless on half the project.
    </p>
    <p>
        I also started replaying Fire Emblem: Sacred Stones today, that games bomb.
    </p>
</div>


<div>
    <h2>Roasted Chicken Drumsticks</h2>
    <img class="center" src="/images/lunch_3_2.png" width="400" height="400">
    <p>
        Working on the chest today so I made some chicken for lunch. 
        I think the best way to impart flavor on meat isn&#8217;t with a marinade, or seasoning, or sauce, but my perfectly cooking the meat to exact tenderness. Exact doneness. Not overcooked or undercooked, but precisely cooked. And that is what you see here. FUCK YEAAAAA (Ok it&#8217;s a tad undercooked but I was hungry)
    </p>
    <p>
        I&#8217;ll post some recipes enventually.
    </p>
</div>


<div>
    <h2>Informatica Interview</h2>
    <p>
        So I had a second round interview with Informatica today for the software developer position, and I felt decently confident going in to it because I had already been offered by Amazon (pure luck). I&#8217;m pretty confident with all data structure oreinted questions, but today I was thrown a pretty big curve ball and I just ended up being stomped on. I don&#8217;t know if I just wasn&#8217;t feeling it today, but either way this was pretty humbling.
    </p>
    <p>
        Given an n-ary tree where root nodes can have multiple children, nodes can share children, and children can share parents, reverse the tree and return a list of the leaf nodes. 
    </p>
    <p>
        I couldn&#8217;t solve it within the time limit, and even after working out the problem after the interview, I still don&#8217;t fully understand it. 
    </p>
    <p>
        Here&#8217;s a good <a href="http://www.careercup.com/question?id=12219054">thread</a> on the question. 
    </p>
</div>


<div>
    <h2>Chinese Smoked Beef</h2>
    <img class="center" src="/images/dinner_3_2.png" width="400" height="400">
    <p>
        So my dad sent me some chinese style smoked beef brisket. So unlike the American BBQ style brisket, the chinese or perhaps taiwanese style is alot firmer. Also it&#8217;s usually eaten chilled or at room temperature. But the point is it&#8217;s fucking good and its fucking dense and I might have eaten like a full pound of it for dinner. It&#8217;s hiding under the brocolli which I added to help push the beef out the other end. 
    </p>
</div>


<p>
    I was kinda sad beacuse the Warriors lost today, freaking Jarret Jack. But shout out to Captain Kirk for making me feel better. 
    <video  preload='metadata' controls ><source src='/videos/bbal_3_2.mp4' type='video/mp4; codecs="avc1.42E01E, mp4a.40.2"'></video>
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[House of Cards S3!!]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/02/28/house-of-cards-s3/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-28T23:00:05-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/02/28/house-of-cards-s3</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Anyone tryna binge watch some HOC</p>


<h3>I support GMOs in my dream</h3>


<div>
    So last night I came up with an awesome invention, pasta that changes color based on the heat of the sauce. By heat I mean spiciness. So if you have some tomato sauce, the actual spaghetti, or in my dream it was like the spiral pasta you get from sweet tomatoes or soupplantation, gets more red depending on the spiciness of the sauce. So maybe like the flour has some molecule that can detect capsaicin or something and that releases a red pigment. Ok it&#8217;s pretty stupid but I can see this being pretty popular. 
    </div>


<h2>Got some new sausage</h2>


<p>
    <img class="left" src="/images/sausages_2_28.png" width="370" height="400">
    <img class="right" src="/images/lunch_2_28.png" width="370" height="400">
</p>


<p></p>

<h2>&nbsp</h2>


<div>
    As promised, I got some new sausages. Tailgater&#8217;s brats straight from the boilermaker butcher block. I don&#8217;t rememebr the flavor profile but I do know it was dam good. Added some ketchuip and siracha on my eggs, and you know I like that penaut butter slightly melted. 
</div>


<p></br></p>

<p>If anyone knows about OrCad and using Pspice with that, fuck that shit.</p>


<h2>Smoked Chicken Leg</h2>


<p>
    <img class="center" src="/images/dinner_2_28.png" width="350" height="350">
</p>


<p>
    So my dad sent me some bomb ass smoked chicken leg. He literally wrapped that shit in plastic wrap and sent it half way across the country hoping it would not spoil, and thank god it didin&#8217;t cause it was dynamite. And I made some bacon and chicken spaghetti with some tomato sauce, but the pasta wasn&#8217;t from my dream unfortunately. Brocolli for &#8220;health&#8221;
</p>


<p></br></p>

<p>
    Oh if anyone is really familiar with the Chinese Remainder Theorem hit me up cause I need some help with that.
</p>


<p></br></p>

<p>
    I&#8217;ve been balling every day this week since I&#8217;m taking a break from lifting. So I have a little blurb every day. Today I matched up with this huge black dude cause I was the tallest on my team. But this guy was like 6&#8217;3&#8221; and I&#8217;m 5&#8217;10&#8221; on a good day and when he was backing me down his ass was straight in my chest. But after the game he told me I gave him a lot of trouble on defense so even though I felt I was being backed down by Shaq I guess I still played some good D. 
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fuck Hearthstone Man]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/02/27/fuck-heathstone-man/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-27T00:59:56-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/02/27/fuck-heathstone-man</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><body>
    <h3>Secret Saudi Dance Party</h3>
    <div>
        Ok so the dream started of with me walking towards my apartment from the electrical engineering lab and somehow I saw my buddy Allen from back home. Like this guy is straight out of my home town and I&rsquo;d consider him one of my closest friends. He says he&rsquo;s here on a secret spy mission and I end up taking him to the Stewert Center where there&rsquo;s a secret dance bar and inside the bar there&rsquo;s a secret room where he has to dance to prevent the launching of missles. On the way there we pass the Saudi Arabian Embassy somehow. We enter the dance bar and it&rsquo;s quite empty. There were only a couple of circles formed but no one was really going at it. All of a sudden Allen transforms in to a female version of himself and then he starts going nuts randomly on the floor by himself. Somehow we make it to the secret room where I was put in charge of running test benches for underclassmen code and for some reason my life was on the line if they worked or not. So I decided to also dance but I felt super weak and could not pull of any of my typical moves and then Allen transformed in to some fusion of my girlfriend Theresa and Byron where that   person would not cuddle with me and was constantly playing some stupid iteration of the online game Tera.
        <br/>
        I&rsquo;m just rambling but that&rsquo;s what it is bois.
    </div>
    <h2>Ran out of sausage</h2>
    <div><img class="center" src="/images/breakfast_2_27.png" width="350" height="350"></div>
    <div>
        Mixing it up with some store bought on sale bacon and some sunny side up eggs. Messed one up cause I cracked it from too high.
    </div>
    <h2>RSA Cryptography</h2>
    <div><img class="center" src="/images/rsa_2_27.png" width="350" height="350"></div>
    <div>
        I worked on writing a script that performs RSA cryptography encryption and decryption for the better part of my day, so if you&rsquo;re wondering how the keys are generated this is it. Totient is a funny word hehe.
    </div>
    <h2>I ain&rsquo;t Indian Lentils</h2>
    <div><img class="center" src="/images/lunch_2_27.png" width="350" height="350"></div>
    <div>
        Tried making some lentils today, but I used too much water and the consistency was messed up. It&rsquo;s got garam masala, cumin, coriander, and chili powder. And of course spinach for &ldquo;health&rdquo;.
    </div>
    <div>I&rsquo;m outta control</div>
    <div>
        Played ball with my buds today. So much more fun when you&rsquo;re playing with everyone you know, the team dynamic awesome. Not gonna lie I was going hard and going off today, a little like Brodie.
    </div>
    <div><video  preload='metadata' controls ><source src='/videos/bbal_2_28.mp4' type='video/mp4; codecs="avc1.42E01E, mp4a.40.2"'></video></div>
    <div>
        Except I&rsquo;m not Brodie so the result is now my knee hurts like a mofo.
    </div>
    <h2>Coupons for days</h2>
    <div>
        Now usually you all know I&rsquo;m about that healthy life (spinach), but when you got buy one get one coupons for McDonalds, you know what it is.
    </div>
    <div><img class="center" src="/images/dinner_2_27.png" width="350" height="350"></div>
    <div>
        Nutritional content claims I had almost 2000mg of sodium, which must explain why I&rsquo;m so thirsty right now.
    </div>
    <h2>Boring Hearthstone Meta</h2>
    <div>
        Hearthstone is such a drag right now. Everyclass runs a max of 2 viable lists for the ladder and the game is so predictable. If both you and your opponent know how to play your decks correctly, it simply becomes a matchup and hand draw coinflip. I&rsquo;m not an expert, that&rsquo;s just my opinion from watching the recent tournaments as well as from my experiences on the ladder. And off course there&rsquo;s Dr. Bitch.
    </div>
    <div><img class="center" src="/images/dr_bitch_2_28.png"></div>
</body></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
