<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Dream | Episodes of Sleep]]></title>
  <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/categories/dream/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-04-07T01:07:10-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Anthony Kang]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Dreams Are Back]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/31/my-dreams-are-back/"/>
    <updated>2015-03-31T22:59:17-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/31/my-dreams-are-back</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3>That tingling feeling</h3>


<p>Ok so if anyone has ever played Super Mario World then you know about the cape power up and how it lets mario fly. So in my dream I had that cape, and I could fly, but I totally sucked at it. I remember I was flying around Milpitas High School at night with no control whatsoever. When I wanted to land I ended up dive bombing at the ground and I would barely pull uop the cape to spike back up towards the sky. I couldn&rsquo;t glide or fly all I could do was be blown around by the wind in the rainy sky hoping I wouldn&rsquo;t die. The entire time I&rsquo;m have the feeling of flying. My girlfriend says when I dream my heart papulates at a million beats per minute so my heart was probably going nuts during this dream. My friends at school also told me I should go get checked up but they&rsquo;re just jealous they don&rsquo;t have cool dreams like I do.</p>

<h2>Sliced Eggplant</h2>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/dinner_3_31.jpg" width="400" height="400">
So I added some sliced eggplant to my spaghetti today and I&rsquo;ll admit it kinda sucked. I have no idea how to cook eggplant the non Asian way. I could have like fried this eggplant and made eggplant permesan but I was trying to be healthy. So yea today my eggplant sucked.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finished House of Cards]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/15/finished-house-of-cards/"/>
    <updated>2015-03-15T22:46:19-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/15/finished-house-of-cards</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3>I have a lot of dreams about basketball</h3>


<p>
    I had two dreams last night. First dream I was playing basketball and I was able to slice and drive to the rim with no opposition, but it wasn&#8217;t because I was playing well I just felt that the defense was not trying. I was basically playing against lazy people, but at one point I dunked the ball and fell asleep hanging on the rim, so I started bending the rim. I ended up bending the rim, all the way down, and then I tried to bend it back and then woke up. 
</p>


<p>
    Ok next dream was fucked up as shit. So essentially, it started of with me and bunch of people were taking a coding test, there was a proctor, but unless we finished the tests, or finished all the programs, we couldn&#8217;t leave the room. So we could write in any language we wanted, but all of a sudden, this guy next to me was like fuck this, and he water bended at the proctor. Like in The Last Airbender shit. So I don&#8217;t know what was going on in my mind but like each language corresponded to a &#8220;element&#8221;, so C++ was water, and Java was fire. I don&#8217;t remember what air was but the proctor basically went full evil mode like MWAHAHAHAHAHA mode and he earth bended and rekked everyone in the room and somehow his powers reminded me of Python. Before I woke up, I think I was like begging to be spared because I had used Python on my test so maybe this crazy dude would spare me.
</p>


<h2>Meals for the day</h2>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/breakfast_3_15.png" width="400" height="400"></p>

<p>My bread is so messed up because it&#8217;s impossible to spread chunky peanut butter.</p>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/dinner_3_15.png" width="400" height="400"></p>

<p>Baked some chicken wings and carrots. I wish I had some rosemary though.</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't Cheat in College]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/12/dont-cheat-in-college/"/>
    <updated>2015-03-12T23:02:54-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/12/dont-cheat-in-college</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
    Ok so when I woke up this morning I actually deemed my dream to be worthy of posting, but maybe that&#8217;s just because I had fun in my dream. So it&#8217;s like almost 12 AM right now, so I have extremely faded memories of what I dreamed about last night. Going of my notes I wrote this morning, I was playing in the 3 on 3 basketball tournament that my high school would always host. Except I was playing in my current body, so I was basically having the time of my life dunking on high school kids. The other thing I wrote down this morning was studying&#8230;. so fuck that. 
</p>


<h2>I love breakfast</h2>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/breakfast_3_12.png" width="400" height="400"></p>

<p>
    Eggs, cajun sausage, onions, spinach. Peanut butter sandwich not shown. I wonder when I&#8217;ll get tired of this breakfast.
</p>


<p>
    I know I haven&#8217;t posted much about school or any code snippets and stuff like that, but my excuse is because I&#8217;ve been pretty busy this week. But I&#8217;ll be writing a script that does a Denial of Service attack soon so look forward to that.
</p>


<h2>Some nice spaghetti</h2>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/dinner_3_12.png" width="400" height="400"></p>

<p>
    Doesn&#8217;t look to special but this is cooked with 4 slices of bacon so its fucking good.
</p>


<h3>Last stop on the struggle bus</h3>


<p>
    So I had a midterm on semiconductors today, and this is one of the reasons I sometimes I did computer science instead of computer engineering. But anyways, someone got rekked today, he was caught cheating. The professor brough his test down to the bottom of the lecture hall and yelled, &#8220;This kid is wasting his parent&#8217;s money.&#8221; Pretty scary, pretty harsh. 
</p>


<h2>Harpoon IPA</h2>


<p>
    Recently turned 21 so I started sampling different kind of beers with my roomie.
</p>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/beer_3_12.png" width="350" height="350">
<img class="center" src="/images/beer_cup_3_12.png" width="350" height="350"></p>

<p>
    So this beer is an IPA, which I guess makes it more fancy, or more legit? I don&#8217;t really know because I don&#8217;t know too much about beers. But when we opened it, it definitly had a fruity scent to it. Maybe not exactly fruity, but it had a pleasent, nature like sent to it. And the taste was very interesting. I&#8217;ve never had another beer that tasted like it. It was initially sweet, but immediately became bitter. But the bitter wasn&#8217;t unpleasent, it was interesting and it stuck to my toungue. 
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacker or Programmer]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/07/hacker-or-programmer/"/>
    <updated>2015-03-07T17:09:47-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/07/hacker-or-programmer</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Double post today since I missed a post yesterday because I was at a hackathon.</p>

<h3>Zombie Apocalypse</h3>


<p>
    I actually had to do a google search on apocalypse to make sure I spelled it correctly and magically I did. But this dream was freaking brazy, yea, crazy not brazy. So brazy I remembered it even it was two nights ago. So I me and my buddy Erik were somewhere in China visiting our buddy Jason. And everything seemed really normal, just chilling and going around China but for some reason we spent a lot of time on the subways. Like the the only places that felt safe in the country were on the subways, but even then, there was some kind of uncomfortable aura from being on the subway. Somehow, the entire universe we were in became some sort of zombie apocalypse world. In my dreams I&#8217;m always thrown in to these being chased situations where I have to run away. So Erik and I were actually with a bunch of other people and we were running away but they couldn&#8217;t keep up with me cause we had to parkor over trucks for some reason, so I guess I just kept running and I left them behind. I didin&#8217;t ditch them, I just needed to figure out a way out of this. I saw a family of four enter a bathroom and then I saw a light flash from underneath the door. I opened the bathroom door and they were gone, all that was left was a menu on the toilet seat. On the menu was an option for &#8220;go home.&#8221; So I guess I just ordered that and I was teleported back home. But then I knew I had to go back and get Erik and the others so I used the menu to order myself back in to the zombie world&#8230;. I ran out of the bathroom holding the menu and I saw the others and they said &#8220;Anthony! we found a way to get back home! We have to hold each other&#8217;s hand and run to Wal-Mart where there&#8217;s a portal!&#8221; Well I said fuck that cause I have this menu.
</p>


<h2>Tortilla Espanola (kind of)</h2>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/breakfast_3_6.png" width="400" height="400"></p>

<p>Basically an egg omlette with bacon, spinach, SAUSAGE, and rice.</p>


<h2>Hack the Anvil</h2>


<p>
    Went to an hackathon with my buds, but I guess I don&#8217;t have the same fire as the other hackers there so we left early. I mean I really enjoy programming and creating new things, and trying out new technologies, but I guess I do enjoy it enough to go for 36 hours straight. I mean, I want to play basketball and eat real food, not the chain store pizza they provide for us. But it was still a good expereince, I got to try out a Myo, which is an arm band that reacts to different ways you flex your arm, to send specific inputs to a program.
</p>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/myo_3_6.png" width="400" height="400"></p>

<h2>the next day</h2>


<p>
    Ok so my dream from last night, which was after the hackathon, involved me doing pushups and somehow kicking my mom in the face. So we&#8217;ll just leave it at that.
</p>


<h2>Boiler Block Bacon</h2>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/breakfast_3_7.png" width="350" height="350"></p>

<p>
    Made an actual omlette today instead of my weird half scramble half omlette thing. And some nice, meaty bacon from the Purdue butcher shop. And I also like peanut butter.
</p>


<p>
    I have 5 consecutive midterms the following week so I mainly just studied today. Gotta know those pdfs, cdfs, and pmfs. But at the same time that didin&#8217;t stop me from playing 4 hours of basketball today. UGHHHHHHH
</p>


<h2>Spaghetti cooked in meat juice</h2>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/dinner_3_7.png" width="400" height="400"></p>

<p>
    So I had some leftover meat juice from cooking that huge ass steak the other day, as well as the steak, so I decided to cook the spaghetti in that meat juice. This was hands down the best fucking spaghetti I&#8217;ve ever made for myself. I think everything should just be cooked in meat juice. 
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Slice of Cow]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/05/slice-of-cow/"/>
    <updated>2015-03-05T23:03:33-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/05/slice-of-cow</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
    I deemed my dream good enough to take notes on it in the morning, so let&#8217;s see if I can recall it based on my notes. Ok so there&#8217;s this one plaza in cupertino or sunnyvale or I don&#8217;t even know where somewhere around that area, and that plaza has like a Japanese store, and a beard papa. So I was driving there to meet my family, but my car was driving freaking weird, it had no handling. So if you&#8217;ve played mario kart before, it&#8217;s like my car had like a handling rating of 1 out of 10. I couldn&#8217;t make turns for shit. But like I said before I don&#8217;t simply dream, I freaking expereince the feelings, so imagine driving a car that you can&#8217;t turn, and you can&#8217;t slow down, on a regular road. But whatever I finally make it to the dam blaza and there&#8217;s a gym like barbell brigade, bart kwan&#8217;s gym, except everyone working out in the gym was naked. So there were people walking around in the parking lot naked so I don&#8217;t know, instead of going what the fuck I actually was just like ok I&#8217;m down and went to work out in there. All I really remember was the dream was fucking crazy, and this one person had boobs as muscles, if you can imagine that. Also next door was a store selling like pounds of smoked turkey wrapped in plastic wrap. I just kept thinking of fermented meat when I woke up.
</p>


<h2>Breakfast Tacos</h2>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/breakfast_3_5.png" width="400" height="400"></p>

<p>
    Only had one egg today so I couldn&#8217;t make the usual. I needed to eat some carbs also because I had to skip lunch, so insert the tacos.
</p>


<h2>steak on steak on steak</h2>


<p>
    So I had a cut of beef that was about 1.5ft long and 1ft wide so the only way to cook it was in the oven. I pretty much steamed it for around 10 minutes and then braised it dry for another ten minutes and it came out perfect. My camera sucks (or I suck at taking pictures).
</p>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/beef_3_5.png" width="400" height="400"></p>

<p>
    It&#8217;s sitting in its own meat juice, and the inside of that marrow is all melted (can&#8217;t wait to eat that). Cut up with some brocolli for health.
</p>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/dinner_3_5.png" width="400" height="400"></p>

<p>
    My dad sent me this cute little thing.
</p>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/hotsauce_3_5.png" width="350" height="350"></p>

<p>
    As you can see its only 22mL. I thought it would be crazy spicy, but it&#8217;s actually really good. It&#8217;s actually really dam good. Its not like those other habanero sauces that just focus on being spicy, or other hot sauces that are overly vinergry. This sauce just straight up tastes like chilis, it has flavor, and it&#8217;s spicy without being overwhelming.
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
