<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Daily | Episodes of Sleep]]></title>
  <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/categories/daily/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-03-05T23:39:24-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Anthony Kang]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[I'm a Penguin]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/03/im-a-penguin/"/>
    <updated>2015-03-03T23:13:17-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/03/im-a-penguin</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
    Unfortunately I can&#8217;t remember my dream from last night. I remember remembering it in the morning but I must have deemed it not interesting enough to note.
</p>


<h2>Cashew Butter</h2>


<p>
    <img class="center" src="/images/breakfast_3_3.png" width="350" height="350">
    The only difference today is that the bread has cashew butter on it instead of peanut butter. 
</p>


<p>
    So why am I a penguin? Well because my campus turned in to the antarctic. We had tons of snow the past couple days, and when that shit melts, it leaves hella puddles on the ground and leaves the sidewalks and roads completely covered in water. Night comes, and BAM the campus becomes a ice rink. I stepped outside my apartment complex this morning and basically slid from my door to the beginning of the steps. I managed to get down the steps by tightly gripping the frozen hand rail, and then proceeded to shuffle my way to class. Not even boots can help you in these conditions, your need straight up cleats.
</p>


<h2>Qdoba</h2>


<p>
    <img class="left" src="/images/lunch1_3_3.png" width="370" height="370">
    <img class="right" src="/images/lunch2_3_3.png" width="370" height="370">
</p>


<h2>&nbsp</h2>


<p>
    So queso and chips are usually like 4 dollars extra on top of waht you pay for a burrito bowl at Qdoba but if you ask for nachos with all the stuff that goes in a burrito bowl, its the equivilant of getting a burrito bowl with a side of nachos. Freaking amazing. theres like a pool of spicy melted cheese under all that in bowl, and they give you a shit ton of chips. It&#8217;s not particularly healthy but I fills me up for 8 dollars and that&#8217;s not something most places can claim. 
</p>


<p>
    I also had a nice talk with my friend Akshay. Shit that guys got it all planned out. Work after graduation until he&#8217;s 35. Move back to India and start his own company until he&#8217;s 55. He&#8217;s gonna be married at 24 or 26 latest. He knows how much money he wants in his bank account when he&#8217;s at certain ages. All I know is Keenan telling me that my bank of america account got 6 figures.
</p>


<h2>Chicken Thighs in Bacon Fat</h2>


<p><img class="left" src="/images/chicken_3_3.png" width="370" height="370">
<img class="right" src="/images/dinner_3_3.png" width="370" height="370"></p>

<h2>&nbsp</h2>


<p>
    From the sound it makes in the pan to the how it looks on the plate to how good it is, this chicken is bomb. Unghhhh. The onions are nice after being baked along with the chicken. And of course brocolli for health. 
</p>


<h2>Mixing it up</h2>


<p>
    Mixed it up with some box jumps. I&#8217;m about 5&#8217;10&#8221;, which is pretty short in the Midwest. But anyways, the box is about up to my clavicle so I&#8217;d say this is around a 5 foot jump.
</p>


<div style="width:300px; height:550px; align:center">
    <video width='300' height='300' preload='metadata' controls ><source src='/videos/gym_3_3_converted.mp4' type='video/mp4; codecs="avc1.42E01E, mp4a.40.2"'></video>
</div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Got Smashed on an Interview]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/02/got-smashed-on-an-interview/"/>
    <updated>2015-03-02T23:32:12-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/02/got-smashed-on-an-interview</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div>
<h3>Grand theft of my breath</h3>
    <p>
        All right you guys are in for a fucking story today, I actually remembered my dream and wrote stuff to help me remember. First of all, in a lot of my dreams I&#8217;m typically put in to the kind of scenario similar to GTA. If you&#8217;ve played GTA before, if you don&#8217;t have cheats enabled, when you actually get wanted stars, the police chase after you and you actually have to hide. But that&#8217;s just a video game, imagine you&#8217;re in that scenario in your dream. When I dream, they&#8217;re lucid in the sense that I&#8217;m conscious of whats going on, and the fact that I&#8217;m dreaming, but not in the sense where I can control my dream. I can control my actions, but within the real life limits of the scene I&#8217;m dumped in to. So I&#8217;m part of some 4 man hunter team and we&#8217;re wanted by the police and we&#8217;re at my old high school. We&#8217;re sneaking around and I just feel it in my heart that we&#8217;re fucked so I just book it and run through the school, through class rooms and doors and gyms and climbing shit and I eventually make it and hide in a tree. The thing is I actually feel the nervousness and heart papulations you would get if this was actually happening. For some reason I&#8217;m always fucking running away from something in my dreams.
    </p>
    <p>
        The second part of my dream was even more fucked up. I&#8217;m still part of this four man team, but we&#8217;re thrown in some labyrinth to hunt another 4 man team. Or rather, we&#8217;re also being hunted. So we had some gear where we could share vision with each other, so I saw when one of my team mates was pinned against a wall staring down the barrel of an enemy charging her laser beams. But because this is a dream, my teammate did something absolutely crazy and somehow opened a dimension portal where she was and where another enemy was and swapped positions. So then the enemy was going to shoot her own teammates. But my teammate fucked up and the portal she opened closed on her arm, but she didin&#8217;t lose her arm, she just lost the soul within her arm&#8230; So she tried to recover it by siphoning some soul from another teammate. But that teammate was being hunted and he was hiding from his hunter by making clones of himself so his hunter could not figure out which was the real one, but when my first teammate tried linking her soul with him, it gave away which of the clones was real. I was thinking to myself shit she fucked everything up, and then I woke up. Dreams pretty fucking real&#8230;.
    </p>
</div>


<div>
    <h2>I can make a better looking one (promise)</h2>
    <img class="center" src="/images/breakfast_3_2.png" width="350" height="350">
    <p>I was dam tired this morning, so presentation and precision was at an absolute minimum when making this egg sandwich.</p>
</div>


<div>
    <p>
        Remeber when I said my group wanted to make a GPU on an FPGA. Well we decided since we know nothing about FPGAs and nothing about GPUs we&#8217;re just going to do triple DES encryption on an FPGA instead. That way we&#8217;re only completely clueless on half the project.
    </p>
    <p>
        I also started replaying Fire Emblem: Sacred Stones today, that games bomb.
    </p>
</div>


<div>
    <h2>Roasted Chicken Drumsticks</h2>
    <img class="center" src="/images/lunch_3_2.png" width="400" height="400">
    <p>
        Working on the chest today so I made some chicken for lunch. 
        I think the best way to impart flavor on meat isn&#8217;t with a marinade, or seasoning, or sauce, but my perfectly cooking the meat to exact tenderness. Exact doneness. Not overcooked or undercooked, but precisely cooked. And that is what you see here. FUCK YEAAAAA (Ok it&#8217;s a tad undercooked but I was hungry)
    </p>
    <p>
        I&#8217;ll post some recipes enventually.
    </p>
</div>


<div>
    <h2>Informatica Interview</h2>
    <p>
        So I had a second round interview with Informatica today for the software developer position, and I felt decently confident going in to it because I had already been offered by Amazon (pure luck). I&#8217;m pretty confident with all data structure oreinted questions, but today I was thrown a pretty big curve ball and I just ended up being stomped on. I don&#8217;t know if I just wasn&#8217;t feeling it today, but either way this was pretty humbling.
    </p>
    <p>
        Given an n-ary tree where root nodes can have multiple children, nodes can share children, and children can share parents, reverse the tree and return a list of the leaf nodes. 
    </p>
    <p>
        I couldn&#8217;t solve it within the time limit, and even after working out the problem after the interview, I still don&#8217;t fully understand it. 
    </p>
    <p>
        Here&#8217;s a good <a href="http://www.careercup.com/question?id=12219054">thread</a> on the question. 
    </p>
</div>


<div>
    <h2>Chinese Smoked Beef</h2>
    <img class="center" src="/images/dinner_3_2.png" width="400" height="400">
    <p>
        So my dad sent me some chinese style smoked beef brisket. So unlike the American BBQ style brisket, the chinese or perhaps taiwanese style is alot firmer. Also it&#8217;s usually eaten chilled or at room temperature. But the point is it&#8217;s fucking good and its fucking dense and I might have eaten like a full pound of it for dinner. It&#8217;s hiding under the brocolli which I added to help push the beef out the other end. 
    </p>
</div>


<p>
    I was kinda sad beacuse the Warriors lost today, freaking Jarret Jack. But shout out to Captain Kirk for making me feel better. 
    <video  preload='metadata' controls ><source src='/videos/bbal_3_2.mp4' type='video/mp4; codecs="avc1.42E01E, mp4a.40.2"'></video>
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[KOBEEEEE]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/01/kobeeeee/"/>
    <updated>2015-03-01T22:03:57-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/01/kobeeeee</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
    I&#8217;m pretty tired today and I can&#8217;t remember my dream so going to keep this short. Some nice instant coffee in the morning.
</p>


<p><img class="center" src="images/breakfast_3_1.png" width="350" height="350"></p>

<p> Snow was crazy today. Here&#8217;s a view from my schools ECE building.</p>


<p><img class="center" src="images/school_2_28.png" width="350" height="350"></p>

<p> My overly ambitions group wants to make this monstrosity.</p>


<p><img class="center" src="images/gpu_3_1.png" width="350" height="350"></p>

<p> Been feeling the pasta recently so pasta with chicken, bacon, and spinach again. </p>


<p><img class="center" src="images/dinner_3_1.png" width="350" height="350"></p>

<p>But I did watch Kobe Bryant&#8217;s muse documentary, and dam he has some powerful things to say. I&#8217;m not a movie reviewer or something so all I can say is I would highly recommend it.</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fuck Hearthstone Man]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/02/27/fuck-heathstone-man/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-27T00:59:56-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/02/27/fuck-heathstone-man</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><body>
    <h3>Secret Saudi Dance Party</h3>
    <div>
        Ok so the dream started of with me walking towards my apartment from the electrical engineering lab and somehow I saw my buddy Allen from back home. Like this guy is straight out of my home town and I&rsquo;d consider him one of my closest friends. He says he&rsquo;s here on a secret spy mission and I end up taking him to the Stewert Center where there&rsquo;s a secret dance bar and inside the bar there&rsquo;s a secret room where he has to dance to prevent the launching of missles. On the way there we pass the Saudi Arabian Embassy somehow. We enter the dance bar and it&rsquo;s quite empty. There were only a couple of circles formed but no one was really going at it. All of a sudden Allen transforms in to a female version of himself and then he starts going nuts randomly on the floor by himself. Somehow we make it to the secret room where I was put in charge of running test benches for underclassmen code and for some reason my life was on the line if they worked or not. So I decided to also dance but I felt super weak and could not pull of any of my typical moves and then Allen transformed in to some fusion of my girlfriend Theresa and Byron where that   person would not cuddle with me and was constantly playing some stupid iteration of the online game Tera.
        <br/>
        I&rsquo;m just rambling but that&rsquo;s what it is bois.
    </div>
    <h2>Ran out of sausage</h2>
    <div><img class="center" src="/images/breakfast_2_27.png" width="350" height="350"></div>
    <div>
        Mixing it up with some store bought on sale bacon and some sunny side up eggs. Messed one up cause I cracked it from too high.
    </div>
    <h2>RSA Cryptography</h2>
    <div><img class="center" src="/images/rsa_2_27.png" width="350" height="350"></div>
    <div>
        I worked on writing a script that performs RSA cryptography encryption and decryption for the better part of my day, so if you&rsquo;re wondering how the keys are generated this is it. Totient is a funny word hehe.
    </div>
    <h2>I ain&rsquo;t Indian Lentils</h2>
    <div><img class="center" src="/images/lunch_2_27.png" width="350" height="350"></div>
    <div>
        Tried making some lentils today, but I used too much water and the consistency was messed up. It&rsquo;s got garam masala, cumin, coriander, and chili powder. And of course spinach for &ldquo;health&rdquo;.
    </div>
    <div>I&rsquo;m outta control</div>
    <div>
        Played ball with my buds today. So much more fun when you&rsquo;re playing with everyone you know, the team dynamic awesome. Not gonna lie I was going hard and going off today, a little like Brodie.
    </div>
    <div><video  preload='metadata' controls ><source src='/videos/bbal_2_28.mp4' type='video/mp4; codecs="avc1.42E01E, mp4a.40.2"'></video></div>
    <div>
        Except I&rsquo;m not Brodie so the result is now my knee hurts like a mofo.
    </div>
    <h2>Coupons for days</h2>
    <div>
        Now usually you all know I&rsquo;m about that healthy life (spinach), but when you got buy one get one coupons for McDonalds, you know what it is.
    </div>
    <div><img class="center" src="/images/dinner_2_27.png" width="350" height="350"></div>
    <div>
        Nutritional content claims I had almost 2000mg of sodium, which must explain why I&rsquo;m so thirsty right now.
    </div>
    <h2>Boring Hearthstone Meta</h2>
    <div>
        Hearthstone is such a drag right now. Everyclass runs a max of 2 viable lists for the ladder and the game is so predictable. If both you and your opponent know how to play your decks correctly, it simply becomes a matchup and hand draw coinflip. I&rsquo;m not an expert, that&rsquo;s just my opinion from watching the recent tournaments as well as from my experiences on the ladder. And off course there&rsquo;s Dr. Bitch.
    </div>
    <div><img class="center" src="/images/dr_bitch_2_28.png"></div>
</body></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protect the Freaking Ball]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/02/26/protect-the-freaking-ball/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-26T23:30:12-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/02/26/protect-the-freaking-ball</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><body></p>

<div>
    I freaking had three episodes of dreams last night but I messed up and didin&#8217;t write them down before making breakfast so I only remember one. I&#8217;m going to start setting up the tomorrow&#8217;s posts so I can just slap them down on the post in the morning.
    <br/>
    <br/>
    <h3>I&#8217;m transferring???</h3>
    <div>
        So the only dream I remember involved me getting an email in my Purdue email saying that I&#8217;m being transferred to a private local college back home, and I had no choice but to go. When I arrived in my hometown, all my buds from home had been extracted from their respecitve colleges and we were forced to take a placement test. So this isn&#8217;t very exciting, but the thing is that I remember the test with such detail. I was doing freaking combinatorics problems, drawing RTL diagrams, writing code, and doing IQ test questions. When I woke up I actually said wtf because at one point I was deriving a formula for a summation on paper, like that&#8217;s shit I can&#8217;t even do when I&#8217;m awake&#8230; I&#8217;m sure my other dreams were more #action_packed but I had to make breakfast. 
    </div>
    <h2>It has bread this time</h2>
    <div><img class="center" src="/images/breakfast_2_26.png" width="350" height="350"></div>
    <div>
        Last cajun suasage. I promise you guys I&#8217;ll get a different kind of sausage tomorrow. I had some peanut butter sandwiches today too since I had to skip lunch. I&#8217;ll admit I licked the melted peanut butter off my wrists like a savage.
    </div>
    <h2>My chuttigabro Utpal</h2>
    <div><img class="center" src="/images/state_diagram_2_26.png" width="350" height="350"></div>
    <div>
        So I had a totally messed up state diagram drawing so when I was creating the controller module I already knew I was fucked. So shoutout to my TA Utpal for drawing this masterpiece of a state transition diagram for me.
    </div>
    <h2>Ball is life?</h2>
    <div>
        So the team I played with the first couple games today could hardly inbound the ball&#8230; We made these guys look like the Golden State Warriors.
    </div>
    <div><video  preload='metadata' controls ><source src='/videos/sloppy_gif_2_26_converted.mp4' type='video/mp4; codecs="avc1.42E01E, mp4a.40.2"'></video></div>
    <div>
        Later my asian niggas came and we styled on the opposition so that was good. People at Purdue take too many stop up threes. No one ever wants to run the good ol pick and roll or cut to the rim. But everyone plays with really good effort so the games are still awesome. We&#8217;re lucky we have ten courts at our rec center. 
    </div>
    <h2>Spaghetti Carbonara (not really)</h2>
    <div><img class="center" src="/images/dinner_2_26.png" width="350" height="350"></div>
    <div>
        The only Carbonara thing about this pasta was that I used bacon. But I also used the leftover roast pork I had so the porkfat melted in with the bacon fat and then what more can I say. I added some spinach and red onion to make it healthy.
    </div>
</div>


<p></body></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
