<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Food | Episodes of Sleep]]></title>
  <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/categories/food/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-03-13T01:57:09-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Anthony Kang]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't Cheat in College]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/12/dont-cheat-in-college/"/>
    <updated>2015-03-12T23:02:54-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/12/dont-cheat-in-college</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
    Ok so when I woke up this morning I actually deemed my dream to be worthy of posting, but maybe that&#8217;s just because I had fun in my dream. So it&#8217;s like almost 12 AM right now, so I have extremely faded memories of what I dreamed about last night. Going of my notes I wrote this morning, I was playing in the 3 on 3 basketball tournament that my high school would always host. Except I was playing in my current body, so I was basically having the time of my life dunking on high school kids. The other thing I wrote down this morning was studying&#8230;. so fuck that. 
</p>


<h2>I love breakfast</h2>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/breakfast_3_12.png" width="400" height="400"></p>

<p>
    Eggs, cajun sausage, onions, spinach. Peanut butter sandwich not shown. I wonder when I&#8217;ll get tired of this breakfast.
</p>


<p>
    I know I haven&#8217;t posted much about school or any code snippets and stuff like that, but my excuse is because I&#8217;ve been pretty busy this week. But I&#8217;ll be writing a script that does a Denial of Service attack soon so look forward to that.
</p>


<h2>Some nice spaghetti</h2>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/dinner_3_12.png" width="400" height="400"></p>

<p>
    Doesn&#8217;t look to special but this is cooked with 4 slices of bacon so its fucking good.
</p>


<h3>Last stop on the struggle bus</h3>


<p>
    So I had a midterm on semiconductors today, and this is one of the reasons I sometimes I did computer science instead of computer engineering. But anyways, someone got rekked today, he was caught cheating. The professor brough his test down to the bottom of the lecture hall and yelled, &#8220;This kid is wasting his parent&#8217;s money.&#8221; Pretty scary, pretty harsh. 
</p>


<h2>Harpoon IPA</h2>


<p>
    Recently turned 21 so I started sampling different kind of beers with my roomie.
</p>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/beer_3_12.png" width="350" height="350">
<img class="center" src="/images/beer_cup_3_12.png" width="350" height="350"></p>

<p>
    So this beer is an IPA, which I guess makes it more fancy, or more legit? I don&#8217;t really know because I don&#8217;t know too much about beers. But when we opened it, it definitly had a fruity scent to it. Maybe not exactly fruity, but it had a pleasent, nature like sent to it. And the taste was very interesting. I&#8217;ve never had another beer that tasted like it. It was initially sweet, but immediately became bitter. But the bitter wasn&#8217;t unpleasent, it was interesting and it stuck to my toungue. 
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creepy Doctor]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/11/creepy-doctor/"/>
    <updated>2015-03-11T23:50:51-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/11/creepy-doctor</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This morning I actually remembered my dream but I deemed it unworthy.</p>


<h2>Subway (LOL)</h2>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/lunch_3_11.png" width="400" height="400"></p>

<p>
    I forgot to take a picture of my breakfast this morning so instead, here&#8217;s a picture of a foot long spicy italian from subway. I can&#8217;t believe they don&#8217;t do freaking five dollar footlongs anymore. Spicy Italian used to be straight up 5 dollars, now it&#8217;s $5.50 plus tax which is SO BULLSHIT.
</p>


<p>
    So today I went to the Purdue student health clinc today to get my knee checked. The freaking physician I got was a freaking weirdo. All I wanted to do was get my knee checked and gtfo so I could study for my tests but he kept making really stupid Bill Clinton jokes and really stupid jokes in general. I wouldn&#8217;t say I was threatened or uncomfortable, but the entire expereince was really annoying. I felt like I was being like a kid.
</p>


<h2>Lentils</h2>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/dinner_3_11.png" width="400" height="400"></p>

<p>
    So today I figured out why my lentils were staying as cooked lentils in runny water instead of the lentils being cooked and becoming like a thick soup along with the water. It&#8217;s because you need to cook the lentils with salt! The salt &#8220;mashes&#8221; up the lentils for you.
</p>


<h3>Struggle bus stop 4</h3>


<p>
    Took my computer security test today which I knew was going to be absolute rekk so after being absolutely rekked, I didin&#8217;t feel too bad. 
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flip Flops, Non Beach Variety]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/10/flip-flops/"/>
    <updated>2015-03-10T23:31:34-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/10/flip-flops</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
    Sorry if anyone has been expecting me to post a crazy dream, but I haven&#8217;t had one worth posting in a while.
</p>


<h2>What do you even call this</h2>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/breakfast_3_10.png" width="400" height="400"></p>

<p>
    Gotta eat big breakfasts on Tuesdays because no time for lunch. Its that sausage (cajun) , spinach, onion, egg goodness. And you already know I&#8217;m all about that peanut butter. I&#8217;m trying to finish this smooth shit so I can eat my super crunchy shit.
</p>


<h3>Struggle bus stop 2</h3>


<p>
    So my second test of this week was actually not that bad. Considering the labs in this class are so considerate that they could singlehandly make you fail the class, the midterms aren&#8217;t that bad. Part of the exam was to draw some huge rtl block diagram from some verilog code. I finished the exam pretty quickly. When I handed it to my TA, the first thing he did was flip straight to my diagram and chuckle. After that I was like this is bullshit and I just booked it, I think he was just trolling me though. 
</p>


<p>I&#8217;ve also been playing a lot of smash in the HKN loungue. I wish I had my controller here.</p>


<h3>Struggle bus stop 3</h3>


<p>
    Why is history so hard all of a sudden. I actually didin&#8217;t know a a bunch of questions on today&#8217;s quiz. I got 100% on the first part of this class, why is the second part so hard. I guess founding fathers are more interesting than the Soviets.
</p>


<h2>Asian style drumsticks</h2>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/dinner_3_10.png" width="400" height="400"></p>

<p>
    So does this mofo make chicken drumsticks every day. Cause they were ON SALE at the butcher block. So today I made them ASIAN style. I put Sha Cha Jiang and that chili peanut oil stuff along with soy sauce on them. And some ponzu for some acid flavor. You know you have to get the entire flavor palette going. Also carrots and brocolli taste really good when they&#8217;re roasted in the oven. 
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Probabilistic Methods]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/09/probabilistic-methods/"/>
    <updated>2015-03-09T23:34:43-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/09/probabilistic-methods</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3>Struggle bus stop 1</h3>


<p>
    It&#8217;s the week before spring break and my professors decided to schedule all their tests this week. I&#8217;m not even on quarter system so why do I have a finals week before my spring break. This is some bullshit. First test was in my probabilistic methods class. The material was ok but the test tore me a new asshole because half the problems were on the one topic I chose to not review as closely as I could of.
</p>


<h2>Party time with $4 vege burritos</h2>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/lunch_3_9.png" width="400" height="400"></p>

<p>
    Four dollars for all this is pretty good, but I will admit Fiesta is getting old. But I enjoy catching up to all my Indian friends that always come during the four dollar special on mondays. And god dam Akshay was supposed to pay for me today cause I spotted him last time but he ran out of money again so I had to spot him again. Fuck you Akshay. 
</p>


<p>
    After consulting a fair amount of people I also decided to work at Amazon during the summer as a Software Developer Intern. See you mofos in SF. Fucking Akshay didin&#8217;t even know what mofo meant and he was just throwing the phrase around.
</p>


<h2>Baked Indian Style Chicken Drumsticks</h2>


<p>
    Baked chicken drumsticks again but this time with indian flavors. And by indian flavors all I mean is I just put some Garam Masala, Coriander, and Chili Powder on my chicken.
</p>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/dinner_3_9.png" width="400" height="400"></p>

<p>
Recipe:
    <ul>
        <li>Ingredients:</li>
        <li>chicken drumsticks: however many you want</li>
        <li>Bacon: however much you like bacon</li>
        <li>Chopped carrots</li>
        <li>Chopped Broccolli</li>
        <li>Coriander Powder, Chili Powder, Garam Masala</li>
        <li>Fry Bacon on pan until the pan gets covered with the bacon grease</li>
        <li>Brown the chicken in the grease for some arbitray amount of time. Just look at how brown it is. When you think it&#8217;s brown enough then you&#8217;re guchi.</li>
        <li>Mix the powders with ample salt and pepper, and just sprinkle that shit all over the chicken.</li>
        <li>Put the veges on top</li>
        <li>Sprinkle more seasoning mixture.</li>
        <li>Pore some water in to the pan. Don&#8217;t ask me how much, just look at the pan to figure it out.</li>
        <li>Throw that shit in to an oven around like 450 degrees. I cooked for the time it took Trump to play 2 games of Hearthstone. But maybe 1.5 games would have been enough.</li>
    </ul>
</p>


<p>You end up with some ballin carrots and broccolli, and some fineeeee as chicken. Assuming you cooked it for the right amount of time. But the more you cook, the more intuitive it gets to find out how long to cook things for. </p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crop Dusting]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/08/crop-dusting/"/>
    <updated>2015-03-08T23:06:03-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/08/crop-dusting</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Nikhil swiped me to the dining courts today for brunch because it was my birthday, so shout out to him. Unfortunately, I can&rsquo;t celebrate until next week because I have 5 midterms this coming week :[. Didin&rsquo;t do much today besides study and work out with kevin. I think I&rsquo;m getting better at making these baked chicken drumsticks though.
<img class="center" src="/images/dinner_3_8.png" width="400" height="400">
Look at this shit.</p>

<div>
    <embed width="420" height="315"
src="http://www.youtube.com/v/wfmedg6woKE">
</div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
