<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Break | Episodes of Sleep]]></title>
  <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/categories/break/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-03-31T23:12:56-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Anthony Kang]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Theresa Is Here :D]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/23/theresa-is-here-d/"/>
    <updated>2015-03-23T22:51:25-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/23/theresa-is-here-d</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
    This is about to be a long ass post. My lovely girlfriend came to visit me and we took a weekend trip to chicago. All you guys can hate me about how I&#8217;m just documenting my own fun but whatever here&#8217;s some nice food. 
</p>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/sbwt1.jpg" width="400" height="400">
Theresa finally arrived so that means I get kisses now :D
<img class="center" src="/images/sbwt2.jpg" width="400" height="400">
Next day we got up bright and early to take the Greyhound to Chicago. Look at her sad face cause she can&rsquo;t handle the cold.
<img class="center" src="/images/sbwt3.jpg" width="400" height="400">
So I guess I couldn&rsquo;t handle the cold that well either. So I wore her beanie and now I look like a cancer patient. #CAkids
<img class="center" src="/images/sbwt4.JPG" width="400" height="400">
First stop gotta get some deep dish. Theresa&rsquo;s never been to Chicago before so gotta hit up the touristy stuff first! Deep dish is always good you gotta use a knife and fork to cut through the thick ass cheese, sausage, and pie crust.
<img class="center" src="/images/sbwt5.JPG" width="400" height="400">
Then we went to the buckingham fountain but it was off because it was pretty cold that day, which means the water could freeze and bust the pipes. Unfortunate, but still nice nonetheless.
<img class="center" src="/images/IMG_9150.jpg" width="400" height="400">
<img class="center" src="/images/IMG_9142.jpg" width="400" height="400">
Then we went to the bean like proper Chicago tourists. This place always has so many god dam people. Its actually pretty crazy. There&rsquo;s finger prints all over the Bean, but nevertheless it&rsquo;s still really cool.
<img class="center" src="/images/IMG_9162.jpg" width="400" height="400">
Then a nice long and cold ass stroll down the magnificent mile. We stopped by Eatly on the way, which is this crazy awesome and authentic Italian store/market/brewery but there were way too many people to take pictures, and sometimes you just gotta enjoy what you&rsquo;re looking at.</p>

<h3>Holy Fucking Crisp</h3>


<p>This was probably the best meal of the entire trip.
<img class="center" src="/images/IMG_9188.jpg" width="400" height="400">
So this place is called Crisp. Its like a Korean chicken wing place and it&rsquo;s incredible. The menu is nice and simple, all it has is wings, a few different kinds of BimBimBap, and some Korean sides. This place was packed to shit as well. So what you see here were some delicious Korean red miso bbq wings and some soy, ginger, what ever asian combination but it was good as fuck and we ate like savages. Also the kimchi was good and offered a nice acidic balance to our meal. I recommend getting some rice though, because the wings are really really flavorful.
<img class="center" src="/images/IMG_9193.JPG" width="400" height="400">
We are savages. ^</p>

<h3>Beercade</h3>


<p><img class="center" src="/images/IMG_9197.JPG" width="400" height="400">
This place is called Headquarters. Its a beercade, so there&rsquo;s tons of old arcade games and pinball machines inside. All the games were free too, we didin&rsquo;t even have to buy a drink. But we did get this draft beer I totally forgot what it was called, but it was also the first time I ever bought a drink. Or rather Theresa bought it for me haha. But they gave it to us in this glass, and I&rsquo;ve never had beer in a glass before. But it was hands down one of the best beers I&rsquo;ve ever had in my life. It was so full of flavor and the bitterness that accompanied it was actually very very nice. Here&rsquo;s a picture of me playing at a pinball machine.
<img class="center" src="/images/IMG_9194.jpg" width="400" height="400">
As we were walking back to the subway, we passed by an empanada shop called 5411 and we spontaneously decided to have some. Pretty good but kind of expensive.
<img class="center" src="/images/IMG_9200.JPG" width="400" height="400">
Next day we went to chinatown. Haven&rsquo;t had some legit chinese food in a while so this was nice.
<img class="center" src="/images/IMG_9202.jpg" width="400" height="400">
Got some BO LUO BAO MMMMM. Filling on inside AND outside.
<img class="center" src="/images/IMG_9204.JPG" width="400" height="400">
Fried chinese donut wrapped in rice noodle with a sweet soy dipping sauce. $2.99
I didin&rsquo;t get any pictures, but Chinatown in Chicago actually has some pretty crazy shops. Besides the millions of herbal shops that sell shit for like a million dollars a pound, there was this one shop that sold like cs go knives. And machetes. And axes.
<img class="center" src="/images/IMG_9217.JPG" width="400" height="400">
Then we had some of this stuff. Looks simple but the flavor was exquisite.
<img class="center" src="/images/IMG_9230.jpg" width="400" height="400">
Then we went to the sky deck. They have this clear balcony where you can go out on and it feels like you&rsquo;re out on top of Chicago. The weather was kinda meh but still it was really cool. I actually think it was worth the money to go up, the entire tour is nice and the view is impressive.
<img class="center" src="/images/IMG_9258.JPG" width="400" height="400">
So we went to Little Saigon for dinner. And there&rsquo;s this little place at the end of the streeet that&rsquo;s famous for these two noodle dishes. The tomato based one on the left side is called Bun Rieu. The main attraction is the crab meat shrimp stuff. And the right side is called Bun bo Hue and its got delicious pork blood and a pigs knuckle. The broth of both soups were just so god dam good even compared to the ones I&rsquo;ve had back home in California. Absolutely amazing.
<img class="center" src="/images/IMG_9260.JPG" width="400" height="400">
<img class="center" src="/images/IMG_9261.jpg" width="400" height="400">
Then we went to this ice cream place called Jennis. We got three different flavors, dark chocolate, cappucino, and like almond brown butter. Of course I&rsquo;m simplifying this down a little its really like dark dark super dark I&rsquo;m from South America Chocolate, and <em>some fancy coffee brand</em> cappucino, but yea you get my point. But really we only needed one flavor and that was the dark chocolate it was so dam good. After this we went to a fancy as fuck bar that I don&rsquo;t even have pictures for because cell phones are not allowed in the main area! It was so fancy I couldn&rsquo;t believe it I think the only thing we discussed was how dam fancy it was.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
