<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Gym | Episodes of Sleep]]></title>
  <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/categories/gym/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-03-04T00:58:30-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Anthony Kang]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[I'm a Penguin]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/03/im-a-penguin/"/>
    <updated>2015-03-03T23:13:17-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/03/03/im-a-penguin</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
    Unfortunately I can&#8217;t remember my dream from last night. I remember remembering it in the morning but I must have deemed it not interesting enough to note.
</p>


<h2>Cashew Butter</h2>


<p>
    <img class="center" src="/images/breakfast_3_3.png" width="350" height="350">
    The only difference today is that the bread has cashew butter on it instead of peanut butter. 
</p>


<p>
    So why am I a penguin? Well because my campus turned in to the antarctic. We had tons of snow the past couple days, and when that shit melts, it leaves hella puddles on the ground and leaves the sidewalks and roads completely covered in water. Night comes, and BAM the campus becomes a ice rink. I stepped outside my apartment complex this morning and basically slid from my door to the beginning of the steps. I managed to get down the steps by tightly gripping the frozen hand rail, and then proceeded to shuffle my way to class. Not even boots can help you in these conditions, your need straight up cleats.
</p>


<h2>Qdoba</h2>


<p>
    <img class="left" src="/images/lunch1_3_3.png" width="370" height="370">
    <img class="right" src="/images/lunch2_3_3.png" width="370" height="370">
</p>


<h2>&nbsp</h2>


<p>
    So queso and chips are usually like 4 dollars extra on top of waht you pay for a burrito bowl at Qdoba but if you ask for nachos with all the stuff that goes in a burrito bowl, its the equivilant of getting a burrito bowl with a side of nachos. Freaking amazing. theres like a pool of spicy melted cheese under all that in bowl, and they give you a shit ton of chips. It&#8217;s not particularly healthy but I fills me up for 8 dollars and that&#8217;s not something most places can claim. 
</p>


<p>
    I also had a nice talk with my friend Akshay. Shit that guys got it all planned out. Work after graduation until he&#8217;s 35. Move back to India and start his own company until he&#8217;s 55. He&#8217;s gonna be married at 24 or 26 latest. He knows how much money he wants in his bank account when he&#8217;s at certain ages. All I know is Keenan telling me that my bank of america account got 6 figures.
</p>


<h2>Chicken Thighs in Bacon Fat</h2>


<p><img class="left" src="/images/chicken_3_3.png" width="370" height="370">
<img class="right" src="/images/dinner_3_3.png" width="370" height="370"></p>

<h2>&nbsp</h2>


<p>
    From the sound it makes in the pan to the how it looks on the plate to how good it is, this chicken is bomb. Unghhhh. The onions are nice after being baked along with the chicken. And of course brocolli for health. 
</p>


<h2>Mixing it up</h2>


<p>
    Mixed it up with some box jumps. I&#8217;m about 5&#8217;10&#8221;, which is pretty short in the Midwest. But anyways, the box is about up to my clavicle so I&#8217;d say this is around a 5 foot jump.
</p>


<div style="width:300px; height:550px; align:center">
    <video width='300' height='300' preload='metadata' controls ><source src='/videos/gym_3_3_converted.mp4' type='video/mp4; codecs="avc1.42E01E, mp4a.40.2"'></video>
</div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protect the Freaking Ball]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/02/26/protect-the-freaking-ball/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-26T23:30:12-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/02/26/protect-the-freaking-ball</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><body></p>

<div>
    I freaking had three episodes of dreams last night but I messed up and didin&#8217;t write them down before making breakfast so I only remember one. I&#8217;m going to start setting up the tomorrow&#8217;s posts so I can just slap them down on the post in the morning.
    <br/>
    <br/>
    <h3>I&#8217;m transferring???</h3>
    <div>
        So the only dream I remember involved me getting an email in my Purdue email saying that I&#8217;m being transferred to a private local college back home, and I had no choice but to go. When I arrived in my hometown, all my buds from home had been extracted from their respecitve colleges and we were forced to take a placement test. So this isn&#8217;t very exciting, but the thing is that I remember the test with such detail. I was doing freaking combinatorics problems, drawing RTL diagrams, writing code, and doing IQ test questions. When I woke up I actually said wtf because at one point I was deriving a formula for a summation on paper, like that&#8217;s shit I can&#8217;t even do when I&#8217;m awake&#8230; I&#8217;m sure my other dreams were more #action_packed but I had to make breakfast. 
    </div>
    <h2>It has bread this time</h2>
    <div><img class="center" src="/images/breakfast_2_26.png" width="350" height="350"></div>
    <div>
        Last cajun suasage. I promise you guys I&#8217;ll get a different kind of sausage tomorrow. I had some peanut butter sandwiches today too since I had to skip lunch. I&#8217;ll admit I licked the melted peanut butter off my wrists like a savage.
    </div>
    <h2>My chuttigabro Utpal</h2>
    <div><img class="center" src="/images/state_diagram_2_26.png" width="350" height="350"></div>
    <div>
        So I had a totally messed up state diagram drawing so when I was creating the controller module I already knew I was fucked. So shoutout to my TA Utpal for drawing this masterpiece of a state transition diagram for me.
    </div>
    <h2>Ball is life?</h2>
    <div>
        So the team I played with the first couple games today could hardly inbound the ball&#8230; We made these guys look like the Golden State Warriors.
    </div>
    <div><video  preload='metadata' controls ><source src='/videos/sloppy_gif_2_26_converted.mp4' type='video/mp4; codecs="avc1.42E01E, mp4a.40.2"'></video></div>
    <div>
        Later my asian niggas came and we styled on the opposition so that was good. People at Purdue take too many stop up threes. No one ever wants to run the good ol pick and roll or cut to the rim. But everyone plays with really good effort so the games are still awesome. We&#8217;re lucky we have ten courts at our rec center. 
    </div>
    <h2>Spaghetti Carbonara (not really)</h2>
    <div><img class="center" src="/images/dinner_2_26.png" width="350" height="350"></div>
    <div>
        The only Carbonara thing about this pasta was that I used bacon. But I also used the leftover roast pork I had so the porkfat melted in with the bacon fat and then what more can I say. I added some spinach and red onion to make it healthy.
    </div>
</div>


<p></body></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circuits Suck]]></title>
    <link href="http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/02/24/circuits-suck/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-24T18:29:20-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://anthonykang.github.io/blog/2015/02/24/circuits-suck</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><body></p>

<div>
Didn&#8217;t remember my dream from last night. Circuits suck. Stared at a breadboard for two hours only to realize the circuit wasn&#8217;t working because my transistor had blown. The hardware struggles of a software oriented computer engineer continues. But enough of that, on to the food (I need to work on plating).
</div>


<h2> Cajun Sausage Disco Eggs </h2>


<div><img class="center" src="/images/breakfast_2_24.png" width="500" height="500"></div>


<div> Pretty much make this every morning. It&#8217;s fucking good and it lasts me until lunch. Gotta have that breakfast. </div>


<p><br/></p>

<div>I had a homemade roast pork sandwich for lunch but that wasn&#8217;t worth taking a picture of. Currently using my phones camera which is quite&#8230;.. shitty.</div>


<p><br/></p>

<h2> Soy Sauce Roast Pork </h2>


<div><img class="center" src="/images/dinner_2_24.png" width="500" height="500"></div>


<div> Meat, rice, and brocolli. The plating sucks but it tastes good I swear. It&#8217;s easy to make too, I&#8217;ll try to get a recipe up eventually.</div>


<p><br/></p>

<h2> Daily Workout </h2>


<div>Wanted to get a video of a 4 plate pull but definitly wasn&#8217;t feeling it today. Form was already struggling with 315 x 5. Going to take a break from lifting for a week and probably just play ball. I think I need a better chair for my desk cause my back&#8217;s been feeling like an old man&#8217;s. </div>


<p><video  preload='metadata' controls ><source src='/videos/dl_2_25_2015.mp4' type='video/mp4; codecs="avc1.42E01E, mp4a.40.2"'></video></p>

<div>Here&#8217;s a some pictures I wanted to put on this blog but I didin&#8217;t have it set up yet and I&#8217;m too lazy now ></div>


<p><br/></p>

<div>
stole some chicken from the dining court
<img class="center" src="/images/dc_chicken_2_22.png" width="500" height="500">
lamb spaghetti with some unmelted cheese
<img class="center" src="/images/dinner_2_23.png" width="500" height="500">
4 dollar vegeterian wet burritos with my chut jakshay
<img class="center" src="/images/jakshay_2_23.png" width="500" height="500">
<img class="center" src="/images/lunch_2_23.png" width="500" height="500">
</div>


<p></body></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
